{
    "subject": "Kenneth_Branagh",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Peter's_Friends",
    "human_readable": "Kenneth Branagh acted in Peter's Friends.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8167125582695007,
            "question": "Who acted in the movie Peter's Friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7806538939476013,
            "question": "Is Kenneth Branagh known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316034197807312,
            "question": "Name a movie starring Kenneth Branagh."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942665100097656,
            "question": "What film did Kenneth Branagh star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47197750210762024,
            "question": "Who directed Peter's Friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4592239558696747,
            "question": "What other movies has Kenneth Branagh been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4090859293937683,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to Peter's Friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3991735875606537,
            "question": "Was Peter's Friends a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27549490332603455,
            "question": "When was Peter's Friends released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2068326622247696,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Peter's Friends?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kenneth Branagh acted in Peter's Friends.",
            "html": "yago_21969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Peter's Friends released?",
            "html": "yago_21969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Peter's Friends a successful film?",
            "html": "yago_21969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels to Peter's Friends?",
            "html": "yago_21969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21969_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The context mentions that Peter's Friends is a 1992 movie directed by Kenneth Branagh, and in one of the files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21969/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt), it is stated that \"Peter\u2019s Friends is a 1992 comedy drama film helmed by Kenneth Branagh.\" This implies that Kenneth Branagh acted in Peter's Friends."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Kenneth Branagh directed and starred in \"Peter\u2019s Friends.\" Specifically, document 141.txt mentions Kenneth Branagh as the director and one of the stars. Document 29.txt also confirms his role as a star in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}